Isn't that him?
Who stirred up the social
media in the first semester?
Live from Hankuk University's
basketball club meeting.
A freshman broke the hierarchy
at the meeting and left.
The basketball club president
is fuming over this.
Do we have to follow all the
basketball club's decisions?
Hey, freshman.
This is how you join our club.
Okay?
Is having a drink
really that hard?
Why are you forcing
people to drink
something with someone's spit?
This ridiculous rule.
I heard the basketball club
president made it.
Please make sure
to tell him clearly.
A leader
doesn't just throw
their weight around.
This always cracks me up.
Please make sure
to tell him clearly.
A leader doesn't just
throw their weight around.
It doesn't sound
the same at all, okay?
I'm really grateful to him.
If not for him, Cheol-myeong
would still be the president.
Everyone's loved it
since you became president.
Not since I took over, Dongho.
What?
I've always been loved.
Didn't you say
you had a class?
Right.
I hate summer.
And those cicadas
just won't shut up.
What are those people
having so much fun about?